<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Groups on Stadial's Site!</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/categories/groups/</link><description>Recent content in Groups on Stadial's Site!</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stadial.github.io/categories/groups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Engineering Groups</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/eng-groups/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/eng-groups/</guid><description>To add links, please send an email to kfulain.uphrj[at]aleeas.com and expect updates in ~24hrs.
Format: Course-ID - Course Name General Group: Whatsapp Section 1: Whatsapp Section 2: Whatsapp Section 3: Whatsapp English &amp;amp; Managment Eng133 - English Composition I Eng134 - English Composition II Eng138 - Funds. Of Speech Communication Eng137 - Technical Writing MGT292 - Managment Funds. &amp;amp; Skills Math Math144 - Calculus I Math145 - Calculus II Math240 - Differential Equations Math240 - Multivariate Calculus General Group: N/A Section 1: N/A Section 2: N/A Section 3: Whatsapp Math215 - Math for EE General Engineering Engr106 - Engineering Graphics Engr100 - Intro to Engineering Engr105 - Engineering Computing &amp;amp; Skills Engr304 - Probability &amp;amp; Statistics for Engineers Engr310 - Numerical Methods Engr223 - Engineering Mechanics Engr307 - Engineering Economics Engr303 - Thermo Fluids Engr205 - Material Science General Science Phys140 General Phyics I Phys144 General Phyics I Lab Phys141 General Phyics II Phys144 General Phyics II Lab Chem140 General Chemistry I Chem142 General Chemistry II Chem143 General Chemistry II Lab Electrical Engineering 3rd Semester EE231 - Digital Logic Design EE232 - Digital Logic Design Lab EE241 - Electric Circuit I EE247 - Electric Circuit Lab 4th Semester EE242 - Electric Circuit II EE243 - Electronics I EE248 - Electronic Circuit Lab 5th Semester EE233 - Microprocessors EE234 - Microprocessors Lab EE330 - Signals and Systems EE331 - Engineering Electromagnetism EE244 - Electronics II 6th Semester EE333 - Comm.</description></item></channel></rss>