<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Stadial's Site!</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Stadial's Site!</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stadial.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Engineering Groups</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/eng-groups/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/eng-groups/</guid><description>To add links, please send an email to kfulain.uphrj[at]aleeas.com and expect updates in ~24hrs.
Format: Course-ID - Course Name General Group: Whatsapp Section 1: Whatsapp Section 2: Whatsapp Section 3: Whatsapp English &amp;amp; Managment Eng133 - English Composition I Eng134 - English Composition II Eng138 - Funds. Of Speech Communication Eng137 - Technical Writing MGT292 - Managment Funds. &amp;amp; Skills Math Math144 - Calculus I Math145 - Calculus II Math240 - Differential Equations Math240 - Multivariate Calculus General Group: N/A Section 1: N/A Section 2: N/A Section 3: Whatsapp Math215 - Math for EE General Engineering Engr106 - Engineering Graphics Engr100 - Intro to Engineering Engr105 - Engineering Computing &amp;amp; Skills Engr304 - Probability &amp;amp; Statistics for Engineers Engr310 - Numerical Methods Engr223 - Engineering Mechanics Engr307 - Engineering Economics Engr303 - Thermo Fluids Engr205 - Material Science General Science Phys140 General Phyics I Phys144 General Phyics I Lab Phys141 General Phyics II Phys144 General Phyics II Lab Chem140 General Chemistry I Chem142 General Chemistry II Chem143 General Chemistry II Lab Electrical Engineering 3rd Semester EE231 - Digital Logic Design EE232 - Digital Logic Design Lab EE241 - Electric Circuit I EE247 - Electric Circuit Lab 4th Semester EE242 - Electric Circuit II EE243 - Electronics I EE248 - Electronic Circuit Lab 5th Semester EE233 - Microprocessors EE234 - Microprocessors Lab EE330 - Signals and Systems EE331 - Engineering Electromagnetism EE244 - Electronics II 6th Semester EE333 - Comm.</description></item><item><title>Digital Logic Design - EE232</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/digital-logic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/digital-logic/</guid><description>In the formless days, long before the rise of internet, all spells were woven of pure mistery, all circuits were analog, and death was common. Many engineers were disfigured by the insane amount of math, found crumpled at the center of a circle of twisted, room sized analog computers, and vacuum-tubed op-amps which burned unceasing in the pooling of madness; some disappeared entirely, or wandered about complexity, sun never touching their skin, breath never warming air.</description></item><item><title>Final Exam: Engineering Programming - CS204</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/engineering-programing/final-exam/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/engineering-programing/final-exam/</guid><description>Exam overview Reread my other post CS204, and keep on prayin.
Also read the DISCLAIMER!
Ze Exam Section 1 MCQs This section was Multiple Choice Questions.
??? is a choice that I forgot :')
Which of the following is NOT a logical operator? &amp;amp; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; || ! Show Answer &amp;amp;
Which of the following transfers control to the calling function? switch return goto ??? Show Answer return</description></item><item><title>Engineering Programming - CS204</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/engineering-programing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/engineering-programing/</guid><description>Long ago, on Svalbard, when you were a young witch of forty-three, your mother took your unscarred wrists in her hands, and spoke:
Stadial, born of the sea-wind through the spruce
Stadial, green-tinged offshoot of my bough, joy and burden of my life
Stadial, fierce and clever, may our clan’s wisdom be yours:
Never Code in C++
But C++ has coded you, word has spread about CS204. You make a mental note to avoid this course, but reassure the course is waiting for you.</description></item></channel></rss>