<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Stadial's Site!</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Stadial's Site!</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stadial.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Math for EE: Quiz 1</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem4/mathee/quiz1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem4/mathee/quiz1/</guid><description>Quiz was pretty simple but long ;)
Here we go: $$ A = \begin{bmatrix} 1 &amp;amp; 2 &amp;amp; 3 \\ 0 &amp;amp; 1 &amp;amp; 2 \\ 1 &amp;amp; 2 &amp;amp; 3 \\ \end{bmatrix} $$
$$ B = \begin{bmatrix} 3 &amp;amp; 1 &amp;amp; 5 \\ 1 &amp;amp; 0 &amp;amp; 2 \\ 5 &amp;amp; 6 &amp;amp; 1 \\ \end{bmatrix} $$
Find $(A-B)^2$ and $(A+B)^2$
Solution This is left as an exercise to the reader ;)</description></item><item><title>Circuits II: Lecture 2</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem4/circuits2/lecture2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem4/circuits2/lecture2/</guid><description>tl;dr The lecture introduced the matrix notation for KCL, i.e. G-Matrices
smthn smthn Read the slides and the book section 3.6
Topics covered: What is conductance $G$ $[G][V]=[I]$ why does ground not matter (mathematically) doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter in a sense that we don&amp;rsquo;t use that node for deriving equations, also that it doens&amp;rsquo;t need to be zero Homework As usual, (isn&amp;rsquo;t it usual if it happend once?) you can find the Homework in both PDF and $\LaTeX$</description></item><item><title>Circuits II: Lecture 1</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem4/circuits2/lecture1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem4/circuits2/lecture1/</guid><description>tl;dr The lecture introduced the matrix notation for KVL
Basics As we already know from Circuit I, applying KVL&amp;rsquo;s law to a mesh is given by the equation:
$$ \sum{v} = 0 $$
Which can be expanded further, using ohm&amp;rsquo;s law $V=IR$.
$$ \sum{R_S I_S} - \sum{R_m I_m} = \sum{V_s} $$
Where $R_S$ and $I_S$ are the resistance and currents in the mesh, $R_m$ and $I_m$ are the resistance and currents in the mesh that are shared between other meshs, and $v_S$ is is the source voltage (more on polarity later).</description></item><item><title>Engineering Groups</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/eng-groups/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/eng-groups/</guid><description>To add links, please send an email to kfulain.uphrj[at]aleeas.com and expect updates in ~24hrs.
Or join The Whatsapp Group!
Format: Course-ID - Course Name General Group: Whatsapp Section 1: Whatsapp Section 2: Whatsapp Section 3: Whatsapp English &amp;amp; Managment Eng133 - English Composition I Eng134 - English Composition II Eng138 - Funds. Of Speech Communication Eng137 - Technical Writing MGT292 - Managment Funds. &amp;amp; Skills General Group: Whatsapp Math Math240 - Differential Equations General Group: N/A Section 3: Whatsapp Math240 - Multivariate Calculus General Group: N/A Section 3: Whatsapp Math215 - Math for EE General Engineering Engr223 - Engineering Mechanics General Group: Whatsapp Engr307 - Engineering Economics General Group: Whatsapp Engr205 - Material Science General Group: Whatsapp Mechanical Engineering It will be arranged soon (TM)</description></item><item><title>Digital Logic Design - EE232</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/digital-logic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/digital-logic/</guid><description>In the formless days, long before the rise of internet, all spells were woven of pure mistery, all circuits were analog, and death was common. Many engineers were disfigured by the insane amount of math, found crumpled at the center of a circle of twisted, room sized analog computers, and vacuum-tubed op-amps which burned unceasing in the pooling of madness; some disappeared entirely, or wandered about complexity, sun never touching their skin, breath never warming air.</description></item><item><title>Final Exam: Digital Logic Design - EE232</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/digital-logic/final-exam/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/digital-logic/final-exam/</guid><description>This is going to be wild!
Question 1: Part A: Design a combinational circuit that counts the Numbers of 1&amp;rsquo;s in 7-bit ($I_0$ $I_1$, &amp;hellip; $I_6$.) input and has 3-bit output. ($O_0$, $O_1$, $O_3$). And write the input equations.
Show Answer Execuse the messy wiring!
$$O_0 = I_0 \oplus I_1 \oplus I_2 &amp;hellip; \oplus I_7 $$ $$O_1 = $$ left as an exercise to the reader $$O_3 = $$ left as an exercise to the reader</description></item><item><title>Final Exam: Engineering Programming - CS204</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/engineering-programing/final-exam/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/engineering-programing/final-exam/</guid><description>Exam overview Reread my other post CS204, and keep on prayin.
Also read the DISCLAIMER!
Ze Exam Section 1 MCQs This section was Multiple Choice Questions.
??? is a choice that I forgot :')
Which of the following is NOT a logical operator? &amp;amp; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; || ! Show Answer &amp;amp;
Which of the following transfers control to the calling function? switch return goto ??? Show Answer return</description></item><item><title>Engineering Programming - CS204</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/engineering-programing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/engineering-programing/</guid><description>Long ago, on Svalbard, when you were a young witch of forty-three, your mother took your unscarred wrists in her hands, and spoke:
Stadial, born of the sea-wind through the spruce
Stadial, green-tinged offshoot of my bough, joy and burden of my life
Stadial, fierce and clever, may our clan’s wisdom be yours:
Never Code in C++
But C++ has coded you, word has spread about CS204. You make a mental note to avoid this course, but reassure the course is waiting for you.</description></item></channel></rss>