<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Course on Stadial's Site!</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/categories/course/</link><description>Recent content in Course on Stadial's Site!</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stadial.github.io/categories/course/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Circuits - EE241</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/circuits1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/circuits1/</guid><description>OK, got no time rn, so there is no catchy intro :')
feel free to read this one tho
Stay tuned! (don&amp;rsquo;t stay tuned actually, won&amp;rsquo;t update it)
What does this page have then? Scroll down fren, the final project await you!
ofc i didn&amp;rsquo;t do the project alone, so I don&amp;rsquo;t claim credits for it all!
Also check disclaimer! DON&amp;rsquo;T USE THIS FOR ACADEMIC DISHONESTY!</description></item><item><title>Digital Logic Design - EE232</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/digital-logic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/digital-logic/</guid><description>In the formless days, long before the rise of internet, all spells were woven of pure mistery, all circuits were analog, and death was common. Many engineers were disfigured by the insane amount of math, found crumpled at the center of a circle of twisted, room sized analog computers, and vacuum-tubed op-amps which burned unceasing in the pooling of madness; some disappeared entirely, or wandered about complexity, sun never touching their skin, breath never warming air.</description></item><item><title>Engineering Programming - CS204</title><link>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/engineering-programing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stadial.github.io/p/sem3/engineering-programing/</guid><description>Long ago, on Svalbard, when you were a young witch of forty-three, your mother took your unscarred wrists in her hands, and spoke:
Stadial, born of the sea-wind through the spruce
Stadial, green-tinged offshoot of my bough, joy and burden of my life
Stadial, fierce and clever, may our clan’s wisdom be yours:
Never Code in C++
But C++ has coded you, word has spread about CS204. You make a mental note to avoid this course, but reassure the course is waiting for you.</description></item></channel></rss>